Hello, my friends, welcome to this 3D printing
in Chinese.
It's true that today we are not just going
to study the software,
we are actually going to have the right to
pay for your real superpower.
You want to see that your brain is in the
sky,
even if it's a little crazy,
you can just take it into your hands,
is it super cool?
And what we are going to use today is Tinkercad,
the kind of ice cream in it.
You can imagine how much of your brain is
in the 3D printing in Chinese.
How is it? Are you ready to challenge it?
Then we will directly go out
Did you see the blue super-triple Mario swimming
pool in the blue?
Yes, he is the one who brought us into the
three-dimensional school of magic
He will take us and you will find that
Wow, it's so hard to complete the three-dimensional
design
We will start learning from the most basic
magic
Then once you step on the stretch of a broken
difficulty
The guarantee that you can buy a newck from
a three-off pair of shoes
You can easily put in a set of different
designs
Ok, please read it safely
Our magic theory is now busy
On the first and foremost, the three-off
world is
Absolutely impossible
Do you know that it's usually said we're
only talking about common and also common,
isn't it?
But in the history of three-off
We have a super mysterious thing called high-speed
Let's think about it
If you are now driving on a car on the ground
The car front, the back, the left, and the
right
This is actually in our X-Jow and Y-Jow on
the screen
But if your car suddenly fell down, it will
fall down
It turns into a helicopter directly flying
to the air
This net on the fly, the direction of the
net fell
is the ZZZ in the world of 3D mode.
As long as you understand X, Y, Z,
the whole power supply will be in your control
room.
When you talk about control room,
there is a called ViewCube in Tinkercat.
It is the small one in the corner of the
corner.
It is like a movie with you floating in the
air.
You may ask, why do we need it?
Because in the world of 3D,
Your eyes are very easy to be fooled
Sometimes you look at it from the right side
It's a good idea for both eyes
Just turn it over and look
Eh?
At the top of the screen
It's definitely floating in the air
It's directly turned into a wide-angle lens
So
I'm going to turn on this ViewCube to check
your mode
This is every 3D mode
Must be a good habit
OK
Now we're going to learn how to play the
sticky touch mode
In the Tinkercat
形状其实主要分成两种,一种叫做实体,另有一种叫做孔洞
实体超好动的就像是你手边一块一块真实存在的彩色粘土或激木,你可以把他们拼拼臭臭不断叠加
那孔洞又是什么呢?嘿嘿,你可以把它想象成一个超级神奇的隐形饼干模具
当你把这个模具压在实体粘土上的时候,它就会把那块形状给一口吃掉,或者说把它挖空
It is simple to say that the body is used
to increase the material, and the fear is
to use it to reduce the punishment.
However, many people who just started learning,
when they woke up,
they often met a big devil who was a king
of the national school.
That is, Mimimi has already taken the fear
of the fear of being trapped in the way.
Why is it still so fast that it does not
have any fear?
In fact, the most important secret is that
You have to put a method called the principle
of the whole body
You have to use the water to put the body
and the fear of the same time
Then put the pattern on the surface
In the moment that you press it down, it
falls
The shape of the nose mask will really move
the place of the Chongde
If you want to remember this sentence, there
is no principle, there is no action
Next, we are going to face a situation where
everyone is in the worst state.
When you have a hard time designing for two
situations,
if you want to make them stand up all the
time in the middle of the battlefield,
you will be in the mood for the next attack.
My god, two cameras are just like a horror
car in the oil oil circle.
The big ones will run away, the small ones
will also fly away,
and the whole area of ​​the whole area of
​​the original image.
You must think that it's a good idea.
Why can't you control it when it's right?
Don't worry. I want to teach you a method
of
superhuman knowledge.
When you choose two parts,
and when you're right,
stop first.
Don't keep the right direction.
You have to use the right direction first.
You want to keep the main part of the main
part.
For example, the big part.
This time, you'll see the big part.
The outer part is damaged.
This represents
That's right, he has already lost the magic
of ice and death on the ground.
Then you go to pick the black one at the
same time.
This time, just let the little circle pass
by and the big circle will not run away.
This is really very practical, you must learn
to come up with it.
After you make the position, you can adjust
the size of the shape, which is also a question.
We often need to put a strong point in it,
or a small one, right?
If you directly use the white point of the
red line,
if you don't want to close your eyes,
or if you have a strong body,
it may become a strange long body
or it's directly pressed and become a big
nose.
How do you make it perfect to become a big
nose?
Tell you a secret.
There is a super-alcoholic called shift sword
on your sword.
As long as you're in the white point,
you don't let go of the shift sword in time.
No matter how you pull it,
it will maintain the perfect proportion.
It will definitely not change, so don't try
it next time.
Wow, it's over $1,000.
When you finally complete the super cool
model design in the store,
is it going to come out right away?
Wait, don't worry.
Do you know?
The 3D-line machine is actually like a foreign
person.
He can only see the picture of TinkerCat.
So we need to turn the design into a language
he understands.
And this transfer language bag is called
STL.
It will appear as STO
Just like the new blood structure of your
heart
It will include a three-dimensional lens
It can be completely read from the blue picture
This is the most important step for you to
change your mind
The blue picture is ready
But before giving the answer to the question
We have to come up with a small mistake
Think about it
Three-dimensional lens
Can you use the digital talent in the air
Can you use the digital talent?
You also know
Of course not
Because on the floor
If your model has a long-awaited knife or
a hole in the hole,
when the knife is in the hole, it will directly
fall down.
The last thing you will do is to become a
terrible person.
Let's call it a big demon king.
What should we do if there is a hole?
At this time, please subscribe to the channel.
It is also a slicer to send out his super
body.
Then you can put it in the box
In the case of the temporary printing
Of course, you will find that your model
has the space
It will automatically appear on the bottom
of the screen
A piece of printing to help you to capture
the material in the space
You can print out the parts of the temporary
printing
And the best thing is, do you know
After the printing is completed, the model
is冷
You only have to use hand or tool to print
these temporary printing
It's just a piece of cake, a perfect shape,
and it's all over the cake, isn't it?
In addition to sesame seeds, there is still
a very important method to cut the body.
That is to decide how long the shape of the
cake will last, which is how much each layer
will last.
This feeling is super effective now.
If you set the height of the cake higher,
the speed will be as fast as the cake.
It will soon get better.
But the shape of the cake looks like one
by one.
The mold is very low.
If you set up a relatively thin layer, you
still need to spend a lot of time slowly,
but the surface of the surface will be super
flat and soft.
If you want to drink a glass of alcohol,
use thin layer to make sure it will be very
very beautiful.
Let me share with you the three sides of
the video.
The first one is sweet greenery.
In fact, you don't need to completely wash
your hands.
Usually, we set up to 20% of the network
structure, it's already very thick.
so that you don't have to wait for the time,
and you have to wait for the time.
The second one is the edge or the bottom.
It's like helping your model add a super
big bottom.
Let her just catch the old practice platform.
When she practice, she's like walking on
the ice, or jumping off the edge.
The last one is the temperature.
The temperature setting was just right, so
she wouldn't let her brush her head
and slow down the speed.
Otherwise, your model will grow out of the
roughness.
It's so great.
Now, you have learned all of the Tinkercat
superpowers.
You also know that the secret behind the
3D printing machine
is when you have to accept the challenge.
In our Tansuo課程上, you have three super-cool
task missions waiting for you.
First, use文字 to add the correct method of
learning the whole universe
to design a whole world's unique physical
body,
Second, take out the paper to clear the design,
make a sure not to fall into the picture
of a certain drawing of a drawing of a drawing.
Third, the hardest one.
挑戰光癮魔術,
one by one, the outer wall,
光線能夠完美透出來的立體、月球燈
是不是光聽就覺得超興奮的?
不過,這三個人物其實都只是個開始哦
三敵獵應的魔法事件是完全沒有極限的哦
From the point of view of the image,
until you have reached the real product on
your hands,
you now need to give a good point
and we learned these mysterious weapons today.
So everyone,
the three-dimensional community of the three-dimensional
community
take your paintings as a model.
Today, do you want to take the
illegal products that you don't want to destroy
to the real world?
Don't wait anymore.
Now just open Pinkercat.
Open your curious task,
we will see you next time.