Hello, little explorers.
Welcome to today's special team mission report.
I am your special training commander.
Today, we are going to take you on a super fun
adventure.
Learn how to explore safely in this wonderful
network world.
We will take you on a magic boat.
Learn to use magical network tools.
Learn how to find the answer.
Finally, I will teach you how to open the most
powerful safety shield.
Are you ready to become the best online search
team?
Bring out your spirit!
Let's get ready to go!
Okay, let's take a look at our task map for today.
There are a total of five levels to go through.
The first level is the internet world and the
magic boat.
Next is to get on the taxi.
Next is the key to the treasure hunt.
The fourth level is to turn on the safety guard.
And finally, of course, the final test.
Okay, let's get straight to the first level,
the internet world and the magic ship.
Before we start the search, we have to know where
we are going to explore, right?
You can imagine that the Internet, which is what
we often call the Internet,
is actually like a super big net that you can't
see or touch.
That's right.
It's this magical net that connects all the computers,
phones and tablets in the world.
In this super big net,
we can not only check information and watch funny
videos,
but also chat with friends who live very far
away.
It is simply a sea full of treasures and no lens.
Just wait for us to explore.
But to explore in this super big ocean,
you can't swim by yourself.
You need a magic boat,
which is the browser we are talking about.
Like what you may have heard of Google Chrome,
Microsoft Edge or Firefox,
these are all super great magic boats.
You have to sit on this boat
To be able to safely wander around the internet
world
Find those interesting websites you want to see
How to start this magic boat
It's actually super simple
Let's look on the computer screen with our eyes
Is there a red, yellow, green, blue
The four colors are combined
This is Google Chrome
Did you find it?
OK, now hold the mouse with your right hand
Quick press the left button twice to brush
Did you open your magic boat window?
If you have any website that you particularly
like,
you can also ask your teacher or parents to help
add it to your bookmark.
This is like drawing a mark on your航海圖.
The next time you open the ship, you can fly
over it right away.
After successfully boarding the ship,
congratulations to everyone for coming to the
second level.
Sit on the steering wheel.
Now we are going to learn how to control the
steering wheel.
Do you know?
Just like we all have addresses at home,
every website on the Internet also has its own
exclusive license plate number.
We usually call it a website or a URL.
This is super important.
This string looks like a password,
but the English letters and symbols
are actually the navigation system of the magic
ship.
It can tell your ship very accurately
where it should go now.
For example,
like HTTPS www.google.com
This is Google's exclusive license plate number
for the treasure chest.
OK, let's actually input the license plate number.
The first step is to find the longest blank space
at the top.
This is called the net paper chain.
Then,
Bravely press the backspace return key on the
keyboard
Empty all the words inside
Then switch to English input
The net paper you want to reach
One letter, one letter, hit it carefully
Be especially careful here
Don't turn the small tree point into a comma
The last step is full of momentum
Press the biggest enter key on the keyboard
The magic boat will start up immediately
Take you to the destination
Oh, wait, what happened?
You obviously pressed enter
As a result, it jumped out on the screen and
couldn't find the page
Or what is written 404 error
Wow, are you super nervous at this time?
Let's guess
How did our magic boat suddenly get lost?
What happened?
In fact, you don't have to panic
Deep breath
This is like you accidentally
The door number of your friend's house
It's the same number
Your magic ship just can't find the way for the
time being.
You may have accidentally typed a small English
letter
or missed one point.
It's normal to make mistakes in special training.
You just have to calm down
and face the right prince.
Delete the wrong word and do it again.
Press the Enter key again.
The magic ship will be able to find the right
line again.
Then we come to the third關鍵字尋寶記.
Are you ready to unlock the mysterious password
of the treasure chest?
Here comes the most interesting part.
If we don't know the door number today,
What should we do?
At this time, we need a super powerful network
treasure chest,
which is the search engine that everyone often
says.
How do you open it?
You need to pass the password,
which is the so-called key word.
As long as you enter the correct password
to this treasure chest,
it will be like a magic trick.
Turn out all the relevant information about the
world to you.
Let's practice it right away.
First, let the magic ship open to www.google.com
Click on the big blank in the middle
Remember one important point here
The search engine is a robot
If you hit a whole bunch of super long words
Like I want to know where the 10th gate of Taoyuan
City is
He will be dizzy
You must give him the shortest and most accurate
password
For example, hit the 10th gate
Control a position
After hitting the enter key
The treasure you want will pop out instantly
This trick is super useful for finding homework
Now let's learn an advanced ultimate code to
teach you how to combine passwords.
The first one is called AND magic.
If you want to find the learning list of idioms,
you can type in the idiom, then empty it and
type in the learning list.
This empty grid is telling the treasure box,
listen, the web page I'm looking for has to have
these two words at the same time.
The information you find will be super accurate.
The second one is called OR magic.
If you want to find a picture of a cute animal,
cats or dogs can do it.
You can type in
cat or dog.
In this way,
as long as there is one kind of animal,
the treasure chest will find it for you.
Isn't it super smart?
Although exploration is fun,
it is also full of dangers.
We came to the fourth level,
turn on the safety guard.
The sea of ​​the internet is full of big wild
wolves.
We must learn how to protect ourselves.
Here, everyone must
listen carefully.
In order not to be eaten by the wolf, we have
three top-secret rules.
First, you must never tell your real name, which
school you are studying in,
and your phone number to strangers on the Internet.
You must hide your own secrets.
Second, if the netizens you know ask you out,
you must not meet them alone.
Third, if you see a screen that randomly pops
out of the window and says,
Congratulations, you've won a big prize.
Or all kinds of weird links.
Don't make a mess and don't download it.
Because those are usually the traps set by the
wolf.
It will make your computer poisoned.
Of course, as an excellent team member,
In addition to protecting yourself,
We also have to be a polite and welcome person,
right?
So online etiquette is also a must.
Remember these four points.
First, respect each other at any time.
Never scold people on the Internet.
Second, be clear when typing.
Don't use that kind of fire news that everyone
can't understand,
to avoid misunderstanding.
Third, pay attention to time.
Don't keep sending messages to people
when everyone is sleeping in the middle of the
night.
Finally, if you write e-mails to teachers or
elders,
you must be polite
and remember to write in the letter
who you are,
which is to count your name.
This is a polite staff member.
Okay, pay attention.
The sudden situation test is coming.
Listen carefully to this scenario.
Let's say you're playing a online game today
Suddenly there is a person who seems to be a
super good player
Send a message to you
Hi, I want to give you a legendary super strong
free sword
As long as you give me your phone number
I'll send it to you right away
Everyone tells me loudly to the screen
Should you give it to him?
That's right, absolutely not
This is a big trap
On the Internet
The bad guys like to use free gifts
Or the rare treasure as bait
You want to deceive your personal privacy
Please remember the golden rules we learned today
If you encounter this kind of situation where
you have to send things for free and also need
your information
Don't hesitate to turn off the chat window immediately
Then immediately run to tell the teacher or baby
mom
Remember to find your new adult to help you
if you encounter any strange things
It's always the safest move
Finally, we came to the fifth level
Which is the final devil
Quick question and quick answer
The final test of the special forces team is
about to begin.
Listen carefully to the question from the devil.
Today's natural science class, the teacher asks
everyone
What is the fastest deer animal in the world?
Ok, now if you want to use the Internet treasure
box to find the answer
How do you input the password?
Think about what we just learned in front of
us.
Searching engines can be dizzy
Can't play a whole sentence
Which two or three key words will you choose?
Give you three seconds to think about it
That's right, if the answer you're thinking about
is the same as now,
then you're really great.
You've got the hang of it.
You should pick out the most important word
and input the fastest empty frame land animal
or hunt a gun and empty a frame speed.
If you do that,
the search engine will help you find the correct
answer
and hunt a gun in an instant.
Congratulations to all of you
for successfully defeating the final demon king
and successfully passing all the training of
the special forces team.
Let's see how powerful you are now.
Your magic boat is ready to go.
The password has also been set.
And the safety guard is on fire.
You are now a truly qualified network search
agent.
So before today's explanation can only end
I want to ask everyone
When you open your computer later
When you open your first online business
What magic treasure do you want to find?
Is it the mystery of the universe?
Or is it your favorite dinosaur picture?
With your curiosity
Brave and safe to explore this network world
See you next time, bye-bye