Hey, young AI creators and directors in front of the screen,
are you ready for the big show?
Today, we're going to make a big scene.
That's right, we're going to use the coolest AI technology
to combine traditional Dragon Boat Festival
to create master-class super-crazy works.
Start your creative brain.
Our journey of Dragon Boat AI Creators is now starting.
This is our tour map for today.
We'll take a look at it soon.
First, we'll teach you how to become an AI creator.
Then, we'll learn about the magic spell of video images.
We'll design the cover of Dragon Boat's music album.
We'll sing the magic spell of music.
Lastly, we'll learn about the rules of traditional customs and creators.
First, become an AI creator.
Your magic journey begins now.
To be honest, if you want to lead a powerful AI,
you don't need a magic wand.
What you need is a magic spell
called a prompt word.
You can take AI as your exclusive film crew
or a god or spirit.
As long as you follow the instructions we give you
like we do when we chat,
the sky-high images and music in your mind
can be changed instantly.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Second, use Gemini to summon the magic spell of video images.
Let's open Google Gemini for free.
Do you know?
The power of the spell
completely determines the power of magic.
Imagine, if you only give a very weak spell,
you can only get the power of magic.
Like drawing a dance.
AI may only give you a boring seed.
But if you explain the details clearly,
like drawing a cute cartoon,
a little boy wearing a red dress eating seeds in the park,
wow, the whole picture comes to life instantly.
And even if AI draws it wrong,
don't be nervous.
Just like chatting with a classmate,
tell him,
please change the background to night.
He will immediately help you change it.
100% precise control of the picture.
Your magic must be collected
to these five key gems.
First, the subject,
that is, who the protagonist is.
Second, where the scene takes place.
Third, the style.
Is it cartoon, watercolor,
or real photos?
Finally, don't forget to add color and light.
Put these five elements together,
AI can fully understand what you're thinking.
Draw a great picture.
The third chapter,
the cover of a dance music album,
that is, the face of the song.
Now that you've got the image spell,
let's make a square cover of the album.
This is the cover of the song
that you're going to create later.
Please order Gemini
to put these four Danwu magic treasures in.
Hot dragon porridge,
delicious seeds,
perfumed sachets,
and blood-soaked grass.
Let me tell you a secret trick.
Remember to leave blank in the spell
and on the top of the picture.
Why?
Because if you draw too much,
the text on the cover will be squeezed together
to block your hard-drawn picture.
After the cover is done,
of course you need to add a big Chinese title.
You can directly ask AI
to write in Chinese on the picture
Danwu Happy.
Or you can download this picture
to Canva
and choose the coolest font
to line up.
Enjoy your creativity.
The fourth chapter, the spell of music magic.
Prepare to direct your exclusive AI band.
The cover is done.
Now let's go to Google Music FX
to make music.
The formula of music magic is different from the picture.
Don't tell the AI band
a long story.
You need to give a clear key word.
For example, what is the style of the song?
Are you happy or nervous?
Which instruments are used?
Is the tempo fast or slow?
And the theme of the song.
Just put these materials in.
Let me show you a super powerful demonstration formula.
A happy,
fast-paced pop music
with a great drum sound
sounds like a lively
Hualongzhou competition.
As long as you input this,
Music FX will turn out two great
pure music accompaniment for you.
Why is it pure accompaniment?
Because the current AI is not very good at Chinese.
So the part of the soul life
will be taught to you and your classmates
to sing Danwu songs loudly.
The fifth chapter,
the spell of magic.
This is the legend of the spell of magic.
As a great creator,
of course you need to know the origin of the festival.
In the era of the war,
there was a poet who loved the country
called Qu Yuan.
After he jumped into the Moluo River,
the villagers were so anxious
that they swam to save him.
In order not to let the fish and shrimp in the water
eat Qu Yuan,
everyone threw the leaves of the rice
into the river to feed the fish.
This touching story later evolved into
the tradition of eating zongzi in Hualongzhou.
In fact,
the story of Danwu Festival
is not only a legend,
but also a very cool scientific knowledge.
Like the chestnut egg that everyone loves to play,
it is actually challenging gravity and friction.
The grass hanging at the door
can purify the air,
and the beautiful sachets hanging on our bodies
are filled with natural medicinal herbs.
This is basically the most natural
anti-fragrance night of the ancients, okay?
But there is a super alarm here.
You may have heard
the story of Xionghuang wine
but in real life,
this must not be drunk.
After Xionghuang is heated,
it will become a poisonous skin wound.
This will kill you.
If you want to be healthy,
take a good bag and go out more often.
Okay, back to our identity as AI creators.
We have a very important rule to follow.
When AI produces super cool works for you,
the system will actually
secretly cover an invisible digital float
called Synth HD.
What does this mean? This means that we cannot
lie to people and say that
this is 100% my own work.
We must be honest and bold and say
that this is the work
that AI and I have done together.
Another super important rule
is to respect copyright.
We cannot directly call AI
to draw a cartoon character with copyright.
But if you really want to
have a Pikachu-like character on the screen,
you can be creative
and change the spell to
a little mouse with a yellow light.
In other words, AI will give you
a big surprise.
If your magic is temporarily lost,
don't be angry.
Look at these 5 ways to get rid of it.
First, write the spell longer and more detailed.
Second, use an adjective to replace
the name of the copyrighted character.
Third, make music with instruments and rhythm.
Don't write a story.
Fourth, AI can't sing Chinese.
You can sing as the lead singer.
Fifth, if you fail for the first time,
don't give up.
Fix the spell and try again.
Okay, future AI masters.
You have tools in your mind,
knowledge in your brain,
and the most powerful magic spell in your mouth.
From drawing to making music,
from traditional customs to copyright,
you have learned them all.
So, since you have all of these,
what kind of unique
Duan Wu Jie practice are you going to create today?
Open your computer
and start creating your masterpieces.
See you next time.