Welcome everyone. Today, we are going to take
a look at the four-year-old self-destruction
technology.
You may think, what do you think of the four-year-old
technology?
I believe that the number of data tools that
we use every day are very high-end.
It becomes a real life-threatening comparison.
Whether you are the new one just now, or the
old bird wants to get married,
this year, you will definitely have a new experience
for the number of data tools on the left.
Let's look at the number of books we have
He has used all of the books in his book
Prepare to take us to explore the world
And teach us how to become a responsible book
Are you ready to follow his footsteps?
Let's go
This is the fourth point of today
Let's take a look at how to send your book to
the end
接着聊聊搭带党案的玄头
再来翻开你的隐形氏位的搭格
最后,棺出来跟立法
非常疼持,我们开始
第一个部分是识よう的
所有缩解阻息都得多
这个还有寻试现到底ilah
我和大家邂 genes
这封比例最厉害的地方
封起冷冰冰的电子游件
直接叫做
对方比例
You don't have to buy tickets, you don't have
to go out and run the game, as long as you press
the button on the button, your text is just like
the light, the moment you send to the teacher
or the student's hand.
However, if you want to push the button, you
have to do a few moves, you must do the right
one.
The point is that the email account is the most
important.
Whether it's a teacher's service or the Internet
in the back, you can't do anything wrong.
And then you have to write more clearly on the
topic of the topic.
It's like a novel by Wang Xiaoming's novel.
This is like giving the report to the super public.
Let the team know what this letter is going to
do.
Of course, even if it's super fast, it will be
tired.
If you don't write the topic, it's easy for the
system to fall into the sky.
The answer is directly recommended.
If you see that there is a 5.0 error in the 5.0
error,
don't panic at all.
This is just a little bit of a small touch of
the system.
Your information is still there.
It will be fine in a few minutes.
What if it's not connected?
This is usually your Wi-Fi message.
Check it out and it will be fine.
The memory is not solved.
Next, the second part.
We have to learn how to put things in the dustbin.
And you can't forget the memory of the Internet.
Think about it.
If the email is fast,
Then the price is the picture or file you really
want to get out
You put them into the digital signal and go out
together
But there is a big point here
The free version of the signal is important
Every signal can only be installed on the 25MB
If you exceed it, you can't do it quickly
The operation is actually super worth it
The little picture of the small picture that
the palm of the palm of the palm
From the computer to the computer, your internal
part has a beautiful, beautiful pattern
It's like a self-reliant report, Wang Xiaoming.jpg
At the same time, we must follow the traditional
path
Before the ship is completed,
Is it really true that the case of the war?
After all, the star wrote,
This is my work,
But I remembered a space-shaped past, really
awkward
We will compare
The good thing is that the bamboo is clear
The spring is light, and the case is light and
the sea is in the back
But look at that NG super high performance, this
absolutely is the position
There is no stopping, the body still uses that
kind of ultra-high-light red color
There is even a fake fire news inside
The most annoying thing is the voltage or the
air
This kind of performance goes out
For example, if you take the high-end, the teacher
sees the head pain
The Internet really is like a real life
All right, it's hard to remember that
But we usually have to put those lily-li-li-co-co
numbers outside
This is our third point
In comparison, the Google Cloud hardware is one
of the leading big bags, which is really a big
deal.
This bag allows you to take out the school's
case anytime and anytime.
However, you have to pay attention to the space
where the school's account is usually only 15GB.
That is to say, this is a bag that allows you
to use it for learning.
Please don't put your social media content on
your social media.
If you want to become a big big bag,
You first learn to open the materials to divide
the case
Put them in a good way
There is also a super important action
When you disassemble the case that you don't
want to disassemble,
You have to clean it up and disassemble it
That's right, just like at home, you have to
take it out to disassemble
The space will really come out
Why is this so important?
Because if you don't go to disassembly of the
15G
Your entire digital life will directly kill
You didn't listen to what it is, you can't open
a new Google文件
Even if there is no email, you can't receive
it
Also, please ask everyone to make a good name
for the case
If every case is called the secret JPG
When you want to find a job, you will really
want to cry
The case is done
The last four parts
Let's take a look at how to share the good things
in the bag
The safe share for the同學
All of the functions are set up, like you take
the toys from the material cabinet to give it
to friends, but the most powerful thing is that
you can secretly help these toys add to the safety
of the magic wand.
This magic wand can decide your friend's ability
to simply watch this case, or you can come in
and modify even to beat the word.
The whole power is completely locked in your
hand.
These steps are your central defense network.
Select the application and enter the email to
the other side
Then decide to give them the magic technique
of waiting for them
This comparison is also taught by a very practical
secret
You can point the edge of the edge of the side
Just press the button to turn off the function
of the complexion
Just look at someone else
You can't take your new shoes off the bag
Let's take a look at how big these two kinds
of lines are
If you just want to take a career to test
But the cotton is given to the edge of the whole
line
Wow, that's really dangerous
I doubt that he is not careful to do what you
do with your new blood
How to light up the light
So remember to give people a reference
Forever, forever to give you the whole line
You can only see that this is the safest way
to do it
In comparison, especially remind us
Don't let your food and fruits in the market
It doesn't matter
When your little pig head is done
Or after the活動 is finished
Must be a good habit
Go back to the content that you don't need to
use the whole line to turn it off.
Check your share settings and you can really
protect your own case.
Ok, now you are going to download the bag and
understand how to protect it for a long time,
and also learn about the most related cloud storage.
Then next time, when you are going to do a hard
work, share it on the internet,
how much information do you have to set up your
content safely?
All these tools are just the first thing to really
understand protect yourself is the most powerful
water supply
I hope today's content is helpful to you. See
you next time